[Music]
We've got a smile for the camera and in
the pond laughing with the lobies giving
all that they
Bills on the table want to vanish from
sight. Footstep disappear body sleep
tonight. Beautiful pill casting on our
pain. Got the life for but his wallets
remain. Ripping holes in our house just
to sweeten the deal back while we skip
another meal.
Don't care.
[Music]
slashing through the safety net.
Scissors in hand.
Go see and Medicaid banish on command.
[Music]
Telling us it's freedom. But the chains
are real tight.
Stacking gold up high while we give up
our rights.
Empty shells where our groceries should
stand. Empty promises, blood on their
hands, big beautiful bill, cashing in on
our pain. But the lunch once for kids,
but his wallets remain. Ripping holes in
our house just to sweeten the deal.
Feeding fats while we skip another meal.
Don't care.
[Music]